# Sergey Bychok, Front-end Developer

Date of birth: October 10, 1990

Location: Ukraine, Kiev (I'm open to relocation or distance work)

### Contacts

Gmail: bychok.sergey@gmail.com

Skype: s.buchok2

GitHub: github.com/SergeyBychok

linkedin

## **About**

Hello! I'm Sergey and I am a front-end developer with 3 years of experience. I'm a big fan of modern web and I like to develop interfaces with great functionality and elegant design. Also I have a good knowledge in design, usability and data analysis.

## **Education**

National Technical University of Ukraine 'Kyiv Polytechnic Institute' (2016–2019)

Software engineering department (distance education)

Kyiv National University of Construction and Architecture (2012–2013)

Specialist degree in Heat, Gas Supply and Ventilation

Vinnitsa National Technical University (Ukraine, Vinnitsa, 2007–2012)

Bachelor degree in Heat, Gas Supply and Ventilation

# **Experience**

• Hypnotic Response LLC ( August 2014—now),

#### Front-end Developer, Full-Time

- Main projects:
  - www.csmi.hypnorep.com/ html/scss/js (jQuery)
  - www.tipster.com.ua html/stylus/js (jQuery/underscore)
  - www.yougossip.co.uk html/stylus/js (jQuery/underscore)
  - www.expresswhite.kiev.ua/ html/stylus/js (jQuery)
  - www.timeq.com The landing page is written with WordPress, the project is written with html/stylus/JS (jQuery). In process of rewriting it with React.
  - https://www.apination.com/ The landing page is written with WordPress, the project is written with html/stylus/JS (jQuery/underscore).

#### Responsibilities

Developed web-site from mock-ups.

Developed front-end part of the project

Created HTML email templates and newsletters for e-mail marketing campaigns.

Fixed front end bugs (HTML, CSS, Javascript errors).

Created and implemented a custom CSS grid system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.

Programmed css/js animate.

 mamaclub.ua, myradio.ua (December 2013 - July 2014), HTML-coder Part-Time

#### Responsibilities

Developed mobile web from mock-ups.

Created HTML emails.

Fixed front-end bugs (HTML, CSS, jQuery errors).

• Freelancer (July 2013 - December 2013), HTML-coder

#### Responsibilities

Built websites with WordPress.

Created Landing pages.

## Languages

Ukrainian, Russian: native

English: pre-intermediate

## Skills

- Strong knowledge of HTML / CSS
- Crossbrowser layouts creation / Responsive design
- ES6 with Babel, React.js
- Good level jQuery, underscore
- Experience with Gulp, WebPack
- CSS-preprocessors: Stylus, Sass, LESS
- PostCSS
- Methodologies: BEM, OOCSS, SMACSS
- Revision control systems: Git
- Unix Shell
- Good knowledge of UI / UX / Usability / Data analysis